{
    "id": "d06cd73d438a4c76a1f3ea70768b5811",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You haven’t paid the fee, …………………….?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence has an auxiliary it is repeated in the question tag.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "have you",
                "haven't you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d33cfe7f08324466a925d2bf39f6ddce"
        },
        {
            "question": "Janet is here, ……………………..?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence has an auxiliary it is repeated in the question tag.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "isn't she",
                "does she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d929defd34e3474b90cf336ff5d1fb75"
        },
        {
            "question": "You want to come with me, …………………………?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "didn't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f815df71182c461b986818c33bbd88ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "He speaks too fast, …………………………?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "did he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0540bb397f4485ba2be29420c2c635a"
        },
        {
            "question": "They learn French as a second language, …………………………?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "did they",
                "don't they"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b94775bad93a4ecf9edfeb38358d31e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went to Africa last month, ………………………..?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "did he",
                "does he",
                "didn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "588b471602054a61bea0578fc3af6de5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Edison sold newspaper as a boy, ………………………..?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "do he",
                "did he",
                "didn't he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "78a5aa53d57f4906bd0fa7a90c022e74"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked all day yesterday, ………………………….?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "didn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7616ef580e0b48baa7f1cc1aa9b82779"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody came, ……………………………?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "did they",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "14a6af86fe4f4117916f06551622c7de"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children performed really well, …………………………?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "do they",
                "don't they",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d6ad1381107d42198b24a48cbd0fb1e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He never donates money to charities, ………………………..?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "did he"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ac7e8ca70074046b74668fb7dc668ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "You never waste even a single opportunity to blame me, ……………………….?",
            "description": "Negative tags are used after affirmative sentences and non-negative tags are used after negative sentences.\r\nIf the main sentence does not have an auxiliary, the tag is made with do, does or did.",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "did you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e9b8fb6e20a84a4cade898667a0c4416"
        }
    ]
}